JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 13
WE PICKED UP SOMETHING CRAZY!
Welcome to Morioh Radio,
Where today we hear from
"Languishing Lonesome Boy."
"Kai, hear me out," he writes.
"My girlfriend just ghosted me,
and I'm super depressed"
"I think I may've scared her off
with my out-of-the-blue proposal."
"And I spent my whole paycheck on
her birthstone engagement ring…"
So you've safely recovered
the bow and arrow.
Yeah, I found it
in Akira Otoishi's apartment.
He'd been using his Stand
to help himself to a few things.
A few things worth 500 million yen.
Police are already on it.
Go ahead and try
using your Stand again.
I'll hunt you down,
and wipe you off the face of the earth.
You can't get me in here!
Chili Pepper's spent.
Even if he were to break loose,
I don't think he'd try anything.
Mr. Jotaro, what about
the bow and arrow?
It'll go to the Speedwagon Foundation
for analysis.
It'll help us unravel
the mystery of Stands.
Great!
Hallelujah!
Then that solves it!
That seemed almost too easy,
but hooray! We did it!
We're still interrogating Otoishi
about the other Stand users
this thing unleashed.
So stay on your toes, just in case.
- Yeah.
- Right.
The Japanese sure
do know their coffee.
Waitress, refill please!
Watch ou—! Christ…
You have to pay attention!
I look away and…
Josuke, isn't it time?
The bus'll be here soon.
Oh… yeah…
Guess you're right.
Come on, let's go. Upsy daisy.
I wonder about those two.
I'm worried.
Whoa, this cake is top notch!
Waitress, more cake!
- Higashikata residence, this is—
- Oh, Mom. It's me.
Josuke?
That's a surprise. You never call.
Well, what is it?
Well, uh… Y-You're going
to be home all day, right?
Yeah? What's this about?
N-Nothing!
As long as you'll be there. Bye!
Hey!
What in the…?
He'd better not be up to something.
Shit…
I hope Mom hasn't caught on
to any of this…
For Pete's sake…
I said wait until I'm off the phone!
Um, one sec!
Hello? Can you hear me? Hey!
Now, did you just call for me?
Yeah. We'll never get
a taxi at this hour.
We're taking the bus to my house.
All right, here it goes…
I know I sound pushy,
but I'll say it again.
Make sure you keep your distance.
And no talking to Mom!
Promise me.
Paying her a visit won't
be enough to make her happy.
She'll be beside herself.
I know that. And I promise.
One more thing.
I'm gonna be calling you
Mr. Joestar.
Huh?
W-Well, I might as well
come right out and say it.
Well, someone I've just met…
I know this sounds harsh…
calling that person
"Dad" or "Father" just isn't me.
Once you see Mom,
I'd appreciate it if you'd make
a beeline back to America.
Right…
Of course. I understand.
Crap, this couldn't be
anymore awkward.
I know I should open up,
but sometimes you just can't
push what isn't meant to be.
Hey, Mr. Joestar…
Um, you didn't happen to see
a hulking, grandpa-looking fellow, did you?
He just got on that long-haul bus.
BRIGHT DEER
LONG DISTANCE BUS
TO SAPPORO
Wh-What were you thinking? Dammit!
Sorry about that.
You said we were getting
on a bus, so…
But you caught up to
the bus pretty well there.
Looks like we were just
about to get on the freeway.
I'm starting to think
I should've let you go…
straight to Hokkaido!
Ugh, damn cramp.
Sorry about that.
Josuke…
I think something's pulling at my pants.
Oh, yeah? Careful,
or it'll drag you off somewhere else.
Wha…
J-Josuke! A Stand user!
Yeah, yeah.
Two in fact… you and I.
Anywho, where's a vending machine
when you need it? I'm parched.
W-What the…?
These aren't footsteps.
Hands? Handprints?
Oh my God!
Josuke, the Stand just laughed!
Look! Right here! In the sand!
No way I can let him meet Mom.
He's seeing and hearing things.
Damn, concrete!
Where'd it go? Where is it?
It's gone!
Where'd you go? You're gone!
Great. This old man is
nothing but trouble.
Hermit Purple!
Beat it, mutt! Get! Get!
Do you hear that crying?
Over here, Josuke.
It's a baby!
I have a naked baby in my hands.
I can feel it. It's invisible!
What?!
I-It's there!
It's really there!
It's soft like a baby.
I don't believe it…
An invisible baby!
It can't be more than
six months old or so.
But how'd a baby turn invisible,
and out here?
I'm guessing
it's the work of a Stand, but…
Why would an enemy
Stand user turn a baby invisible?
And where's its mother?
It just doesn't add up.
Josuke, I think the baby
is the Stand user.
It just doesn't know it.
It must have instinctively
turned itself invisible
when it was separated from its mother.
Huh?
In adults, psychological
duress can trigger ulcers,
hair loss, and hair greying.
By finding its mother,
I think we might just be able to solve this.
H-Hey, that's great,
just make it stop crying!
I-I don't know what to do, either.
I have some experience,
but that was a very long time ago.
There, there…
Th-This is…
Did you figure it out?
Yes, I could tell by touch.
It's a girl.
Oh right, it's what's
between the legs that counts!
Something else I should know about?
Josuke,
do you have any tissues?
Th-That smell…
I-Is it in your hand? A big one?
I had no idea until I got a noseful!
I just scratched my beard
with this hand!
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
Here is your manuscript back.
I'm looking forward to
those revisions, Sensei.
For now, I guess we'll need
to pick up formula and diapers.
And since she's going au naturale,
we need to get her some clothes.
I'm counting on you, Mr. Joestar.
What? I-I'm buying them?
Of course!
You forget what I look like?
I can't go in there
and buy baby stuff.
People will start to talk.
That I'm some 16-year-old bad boy
who knocked up some poor chick.
But I only have
American traveler's checks.
All right…
Put it on my card.
Sorry…
Now stay away
from the expensive stuff.
I've worked hard to
build up that little nest egg!
Of course, of course.
Welcome.
Can I help you find something?
Um, have any disposable
diapers lying around anywhere?
We do carry those!
Your first time?
Yes, I suppose it is…
These diapers are a cinch to change,
even for customers
living without assistance.
SUPER ABSORBENT
ADULT DIAPERS
You'll rest well with these.
Um… they're not for me,
they're for a baby.
Oh, goodness gracious,
how rude of me!
Of course they're for a baby!
Will we be needing traditional
diapers or training pants today?
Uh… What was that?
As you can see, although
traditional diapers require a cover,
they're more economical and
less wasteful than training pants.
I-I'm not really sure, could you just…
And what about the size?
Size?
May I ask how old is the baby?
Depending on
your child's unique shape,
we have preemies, small, medium, large,
and extra large for both boys and girls.
My, how things have changed…
W-Well, she's a girl,
and when I held her,
she was about this big.
When you held her?
I'm afraid I don't follow.
Unfortunately, if you were
to return ill-fitting soiled diapers,
you would be putting us in
a difficult situation.
Um, understood.
Then I'll take every size you have.
I also need baby wipes,
instant formula, and baby bottles…
We carry both glass
and plastic baby bottles.
Huh?
Glass bottles tend to
be scratch and odor resistant,
but can be heavy for a baby to hold.
Plastic bottles may be light,
but they are not odor free.
Which would you like?
U-U-Uh… Um…
We carry all sorts of
shapes and designs.
We have rocket ships and racing cars.
This one, the baby can hold by itself.
And when you turn this one upside down,
the doll does a delightful little dance.
I-I really don't know,
so just pick a few and…
And what about bottle nipples?
Rubber ones are soft,
but lack in durability.
Silicon nipples are resilient,
but tend to be rigid.
This is our "Choopa Trainer."
A diaphragm valve in the nipple,
coupled with the baby's own
suckling pressure
function to regulate the flow of milk.
This is the made-in-Germany brand Nuk.
Moderately compressed into an oval,
the nipple is designed to
mimic the mother's natural shape.
And just like with mother,
milk will not flow
without the baby's jaw movement.
O-Oh, that'll do.
Whatever you think.
I'll take them all then.
We also carry circular-, Y-, and
cross-shaped varieties of nipple openings.
J-Just give me all of them.
And I'll need some
baby clothes and socks, too.
Oh, and I'd like to pay by card.
Thank you very much.
130,000…
Now what might the exchange rate be.
In dollars that would come to…
If 100 yen is about 80 cents…
Well, in any case.
It's all for a good cause,
and it's just baby stuff.
How expensive could it be?
Goddammit..
What's he doing?
He's taking forever.
By the way…
The girl who got the ring.
What happened with that?
Does no reply mean "no"?
- She's probably just conflicted.
- I can't take it anymore…
If someone from class
sees me here…
Sorry 'bout that, Josuke.
Here's your card.
All done?
Okay, great, chop chop.
Now we won't have to
worry about losing her, but…
Without a face, she'll freak out
anyone who looks at her.
I've already thought of that…
I picked up some makeup, too.
First, a little foundation…
There and there…
You know, she's actually kinda cute.
Beautiful, beautiful!
This will help us find her mom.
Now we're getting somewhere.
We can do this!
Good thinking!
That's what I like to hear!
Now for the lipstick.
Now a few strokes for
the eyebrows and eyelashes…
A little here, a little there…
Why am I not surprised..
A little flattery and
this old man's walking on air.
Now walking around the neighborhood
with you will be a piece of cake.
And since we can't powder your eyes,
sunglasses should do the trick.
It's just perfect!
Here's some milk.
Maybe I went too light
on the foundation.
It doesn't look like it's sticking…
Th-That's not it!
What the hell?! Sh-She's…
Sh-She's gone! My hands!
Her own body isn't the only thing
she's making invisible!
She's doing the same
to her surroundings!
Mr. Joestar! Let go of the baby!
I said let go of the damn baby!
I-I let go,
but they're still invisible!
She's powering up!
This isn't good.
Everything within
a thirty-centimeter radius
has gone completely invisible!
But it doesn't make sense.
She can't be trying to
protect herself with her Stand.
Who could feed her or look after her?
So the effect is anxiety-induced.
It's stress.
She doesn't like to be
handled by people she doesn't know.
If she powers up any more,
no one will be able to get near her.
We'll end up invisible, too.
What a weird heap of junk.
Someone better pick that up.
Well, someone will take care of it.
Not gonna be me.
Look out!
What happened?
This lit cigarette was…
Of course, you can't see it.
What in the devil
are you doing, Mr. Joestar?!
Get with it, man!
I, uh…
The stroller completely disappeared!
And it took the ground with it!
So it is stress!
The greater her distress,
the more she makes invisible!
I think I heard the stroller flipping over!
The invisible baby…
fell into the water?!
Wh-Where is she?
Make some noise!
I don't see any bubbles!
Where is she?!
J-Josuke…
Shut the hell up!
We're in this mess
because of this shuffling fool.
Old senile has-been!
This irresponsible jackass
is my father?
A man so irresponsible,
he had no problem discarding
my mom for sixteen years.
No way I can respect
someone like him.
There was no way
this was ever gonna work out.
You…
Stay out of this!
Where is she?
She's gotta be around here somewhere…
I don't care if I turn invisible, too.
Just touch me! Hurry!
Come on!
She's no there… Hurry!
Shit!
How do I find a transparent baby
in transparent water?!
Josuke, I…
won't be able to
hold on much longer, so…
tell your mother
hello for me, would ya?
After all…
I am just an old man, you know.
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm giving it some color…
The center…
The blood disappears
toward the middle.
In the center… the child…
Mr. Joestar…
No ordinary person
would dream up such a thing.
Not for a strange child.
Not for someone else's child…
This is…
I was trying to look cool…
for you.
HERMIT PURPLE
Well, that was an experience…
All's well that ends well, I guess.
O-One hundred and thirty thousand yen?!
All my hard-earned money…
- You rotten old man…!
- There, there.
EPISODE 14
LET'S GO TO
THE MANGA ARTIST'S HOUSE, PART 1